♪♪♪
♪ SHE'S GOT A SMILE
THAT IT SEEMS TO ME ♪
♪ REMINDS ME
OF CHILDHOOD MEMORIES ♪
♪ WHERE EVERYTHING
WAS AS FRESH ♪
♪ AS THE BRIGHT BLUE SKY (SKY) ♪
♪ NOW AND THEN,
WHEN I SEE HER FACE ♪
♪ SHE TAKES ME AWAY
TO THAT SPECIAL PLACE ♪
♪ AND IF I STARED TOO LONG ♪
♪ I'D PROBABLY BREAK DOWN
AND CRY ♪
♪♪♪
♪ WHOA, OH, WHOA ♪
♪ SWEET CHILD OF MINE ♪
♪♪♪
♪ WHOA, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ SWEET LOVE OF MINE ♪
♪♪♪
♪ SHE'S GOT EYES
OF THE BLUEST SKIES ♪
♪ AS IF THEY THOUGHT OF RAIN ♪
♪ I'D HATE TO LOOK
INTO THOSE EYES ♪
♪ AND SEE AN OUNCE OF PAIN ♪
♪ HER HAIR REMINDS ME
OF A WARM, SAFE PLACE ♪
♪ WHERE AS A CHILD I'D HIDE ♪
♪ AND PRAY FOR THE THUNDER
AND THE RAIN ♪
♪ TO QUIETLY PASS ME BY ♪
♪ WHOA, OH, WHOA ♪
♪ SWEET CHILD OF MINE ♪
♪ WHOA, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ SWEET LOVE OF MINE ♪
♪ SWEET CHILD OF MINE ♪
♪ OOH, YEAH ♪
♪ OOH, SWEET LOVE OF MINE ♪
♪♪♪
♪ WHERE DO WE GO? ♪
♪ WHERE DO WE GO NOW? ♪
♪ MM-MM, OH,
WHERE DO WE GO? ♪
♪ WHERE DO WE GO NOW? ♪
♪ OH, WHERE DO WE GO NOW? ♪
♪ WHERE DO WE GO? ♪
♪ SWEET CHILD
OH, WHERE DO WE GO NOW? ♪
♪ WHERE DO WE GO NOW?
I YI YI YI ♪
♪ WHERE DO WE GO?
♪ WHERE DO WE GO NOW? ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, WHOA ♪
♪ WHERE DO WE GO? ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ WHERE DO WE GO NOW? ♪
♪ WHERE DO WE GO? ♪
♪ OH, WHERE DO WE GO NOW? ♪
♪ WHOA, WHERE DO WE GO NOW? ♪
♪ NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO ♪
♪ SWEET CHILD ♪
♪ OF MINE ♪
♪♪♪